本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译   迷失_绽放    我叫魏碧慧     Marshal同学   小酸奶
翻译   CS小明漫画家   天启章鱼X    kiko   如是我闻
时间轴   Ans   SumenQ      后期   蜡笔小新的眉毛
校对   米小勒      总监   米小勒
北极光
最后的美国国安局作战指挥中心
市民Z在前线情报阵地北极光发回报导
This is Citizen Z here at forward listening post Northern Light.
北极光呼叫威尔森山
Northern Light to Mount Wilson.
威尔森山疾病控制中心  有人吗
Anyone from the Mount Wilson CDC.
我这里有关于三角洲X光小队和
I have important information regarding Delta-Xray-Delta
咬痕研究所的重要信息
and Operation Bite Mark.
快点  加利福尼亚  坚持一下
Come on, California. Hang in there
你们的包裹已经在路上了
Your package is on the way.
你要做的就是签收一下
All you got to do is be there to sign for it.
这里是威尔森山  我是黑斯廷斯医生
This is Mount Wilson. This is Doctor Hastings at Mount Wilson.
太好了  威尔森山  这里是北极光
Yes! Mount Wilson, you have Northern Light.
我们被一大群四级僵尸病毒感染者攻击
We've been attacked by a swarm of level four infected.
我们的防御已被突破
Our defenses have been breached.
四周有通高压电的围墙  大家逃不出去
Our escape has been blocked by a high voltage fence.
你从这里能到达电源网格的地方吗
Can you access the power grid from your location?
不可能  我们这里通往断电器的路上
Negative. There are too many Zs between us
有太多的僵尸了
and the breakers.
好的  我在这里应该可以做些事情
All right. I might be able to do something from my end.
如果我可以进入到你们实验室的网络系统
If I can access anything on your lab network
它和外墙共用一台发电机
powered by the same generator
我可以让它过载断电
I might be able to overload it,
这样就可以切断围墙上的高压电了
knock out power to the fence.
我不知道密码
I don't know the password.
不用着急
Not to worry.
我们是国安局的  无所不能
We're the NSA. All of it.
麻烦快点
Please hurry.
好了  好了  我进去了
All right. All right. I'm... I'm already in.
威尔森山
Uhhh, Mount Wilson.
我们随时可以进行过载断电操作了
We are ready to execute overload.
但是我看到你们的主机和基因序列
But I'm showing your mainframe and gene sequencer
都在同一个网络里
on the same network.
如果我进行过载操作  很有可能主机里
That means any vaccine files that you have on that mainframe
所有的疫苗文件都会毁掉
are likely to be destroyed.
收到请指示
Please advise me.
威尔森山  我已准备好过载  请指示
Mount Wilson, I'm ready to execute overload. Please advise.
如果我这么做  你们的努力将付之一炬
If I do this, I'm going to fry your work.
你们有备份吗
Do you have a backup?
-威尔森山  -这里僵尸太多了
- Mount Wilson?  - There's too many!
你现在就得把我们
You've got to get us
从这里弄出去
out of here now!
可恶
Damn it!
断电了  快跑快跑
That's it! Go! Go! Go!
加油  威尔森山  再坚持一下
Come on, Mount Wilson. Hang in there.
主机
塔潘齐桥
不管你在做什么  都不要停下来
Whatever you do, don't stop.
你以为姐会吗
Haha, ya think.
绕着走
Go around!
太晚了
Too late!
开得不错
Nice driving.
哦  不是吧
Oh no. No-no. No!
怎么了
What?
没油了
Oh, we're out of gas.
那挺有意思的
Well that was fun.
没汽油了
Ha-ha. Out of gas.
弹尽粮绝  还要继续奔跑
Running on fumes.
好吧  你们的车胎好像爆了
All right. So it looks like you got a flat.
小心点
Heads up.
有人来了
We got company.
没错
That's right.
继续走  大家就都能活着见到明天的太阳
Keep rolling and we all live to see another day.
好了  咱们动作快点
All right. Let's do this quick.
好了
All right.
看上去轮胎没事  但它就是转不动了
Doesn't look flat, but it won't... turn.
我们碾过什么东西了
We ran over some fun stuff.
帮我把轮胎卸下来  看看到底怎么回事
Okay. Well help me get it off and let's see what's going on.
这就解释的通了
Well that explains the pull to the left.
你还在等什么
What are you waiting for?
快杀了它  动手
Kill it! Kill it!
好了  送你上路
All right, you. Time to go home.
经历了这些血雨腥风
Even after all this,
它风采依旧
it's still beautiful.
再好好看看这里
Take a good look.
我们短时间内不会回来了
Might not be back for a while.
纽约  再会
So long New York.
下辈子见
See ya in the next life.
僵 尸
国 度
第一季 第二集
.
威尔森山  这里是北极光阵地
Mount Wilson, this is Northern Light.
请回话
Come in.
威尔森山  这里是市民Z
Mount Wilson, this is Citizen Z.
想要确保你们还在工作
Making sure you're all still in business.
三角洲X光小队
Delta-Xray-Delta.
听到吗
Do you copy?
有人听到吗
Does anybody copy?
咬痕研究所  咬痕研究所
Operation Bite Mark. Operation Bite Mark.
你现在收听的是由所有已知频率
This is Citizen Z from Camp Northern Light
直播的北极光阵地市民Z广播
broadcasting live on all known frequencies.
虽然有些频率无人知晓
Even a few nobody knows about.
如果你有任何通讯的方式  任何方式
If you have any way at all to communicate, any way at all.
如果你有短波  长波  暗波
If you've got short wave, long wave, dark wave,
宽频  X频  杯子传声  烟幕信号
broadband, xband, two cups and a string, smoke signals.
任何能回复我的方式
Anything. Just get back to me.
我这里有卫星  我会看到的
I've got a satellite. I'll see it.
有人在咬痕研究所吗
Anyone from Operation Bite Mark.
这里是北极光阵地的市民Z
This is Citizen Z from Camp Northern Light.
我要向你汇报加州的最新情况
I have an update for you on the California situation.
我们可以商讨行动方案
We need to discuss some operational realities.
威尔森山  听到了吗
Mount Wilson, do you copy?
三角洲X光小队  听到吗
Delta-Xray-Delta, do you copy?
我不敢相信我跟所有人失去联系了
I can't believe I lost everybody.
那是狗拖的雪橇吗
Is that a dog sled?
那是人类吗
Is that people?!
我...我想那是人类
I... I think it's people!
感谢上帝  有人来了
Oh thank god! Somebody's here!
终于有人来了
Finally.
零食  他们会需要零食
Snacks! They're gonna want snacks!
他们...他们肯定饿了
They're... they'll be hungry.
去把卫生间打扫干净
Got to clean up the bathroom.
人类
People!
等下  是人类还是...
Wait. People or...
新泽西州  帕拉默斯帕克广场
这些车...
All these cars...
没有半滴汽油了
And not a drop of gas.
屋漏偏逢连夜雨啊
Just when you thought you saw the worst of it, huh?
他们没机会生还了
They didn't stand a chance.
黑色星期五促销中吗
Black Friday sale?
找到汽油了吗
You find any gas?
没有  这里的汽油已经没了
No. This area's been picked clean.
干嘛
What?
来观光吗
You on vacation?
总得有人做记录吧
Somebody has to keep record.
我们可能是地球上的末代人类
You know we're probably the last generations of humans on earth.
这是世界末日  她却当成美好回忆
To us it's the apocalypse. To her it's the memories.
我踹他一脚会损害抗体吗
Would it hurt the antibodies if I kicked him in the nuts?
孩子  你叫什么
So what's your name, kid?
一万
Ten Thousand.
这不是名字  是个数字
That is not a name. It's a number.
这是我的名字  我自创的
It's my name. Made it up myself.
想必也是
Well I suppose you'd have to.
有什么深意吗
Does it mean anything?
是我要消灭的僵尸的数量
How many zombies I'm going to kill.
这可不是小数目呢
Well that's a whole lot of zombies.
我已经灭掉1055个了
Already on 1,055.
靠
Damn!
杀够一万个又怎样呢
So what happens when you get to 10,000
改名字呗
Change my name.
改成什么  两万吗
To what? Twenty thousand?
杰夫
Jeff.
我喜欢杰夫这个名字
I like the name Jeff.
闭嘴吧
Ah, shut up.
大家都去哪了
Where did everybody go?
我看不见任何生还者  除了那两个车手
I haven't seen a survivor except for those two bikers.
黑色夏季  人都饿死了
Black Summer. Everybody starved to death.
黑色夏季时我在费城
I was in Philly for Black Summer.
那时很惨  我瘦了30磅
It was bad. I lost thirty pounds.
我以为自己要死了
Thought I was dead.
那你怎么活过来的
How did you survive?
为了生存我什么都做尽
Did what I had to do.
别开枪  不是僵尸
Hold on. It's not a Z.
别激动  我没被咬
Peace. No bites here.
绝对是正常人
100 percent alive.
你那哥们呢
What happened to your friend?
搞了半天他还有个缺德朋友
Turns out he had other friends of low morals.
把我车抢了
Took my ride.
偷人座驾  该枪毙
Horse thieves should be shot.
怨你交友不慎
You should choose better friends.
多谢指点
Good advice.
我们不想生事
What can we do for you?
你一个路人来找我们想做什么
One peaceful group of humans to a lone traveler?
最好能载我一程
Could use a lift.
一个人可没法在外面过夜
Sure don't want to spend the night out here alone.
抱歉  我们不是做租车生意的
Sorry. We ain't running a taxi service.
你这是要去哪
Which way are you headed?
只要不往回走就行
Any direction but back.
谣传说在纽约南边
Word is there's a horde on the move
有一大群僵尸正在移动
south on the New York side.
我瞧见你们到处找汽油
I see you're scrounging for gas.
好比那句老话  搭车掏钱  没钱滚蛋
You know like we used to say, ass, gas or grass.
意思是搭车得给人好处
Nobody rides for free.
我知道你们在哪能找到汽油
I know where you could fill up.
你最好现在就告诉我们
Now would be the time to share that information.
那地方叫泽西恶魔精炼厂  大概五里地远吧
Place called Jersey Devil Refinery, maybe five miles off,
一下高速就是
just off the turnpike.
你怎么知道那有汽油
How do you know there's gas there?
僵尸爆发第一天那里就被血洗了
Got overrun day number one.
所有油罐都是满的
All the tanks are still full,
放在那等着变质
just rusting away.
那好  带我们去精炼厂
All right, take us to this refinery.
如果真如你所说有汽油
And if there's gas there like you say,
我们会把你带到下一个安全点
you can ride with us to the next outpost.
你们肯定不会白去
You won't be sorry.
这你可说对了
You got that right.
咱们出发
Let's get out of here.
新人跟我和沃伦一辆车
New guy's gonna ride with me and Warren.
其他人上卡车
Everybody else load up in the truck.
是不是以后每次停车  我们都要让
So are we just gonna pick up every sketchy loser
这些个废物搭便车
at every place we stop?
我们这不是就让你搭上车了么
Well we brought you along, didn't we?
再说了  也没人问我有没有意见
Besides, nobody consulted me.
我们不会真要跟这家伙去加州吧
We're not really going to California with this guy, are we?
世界末日就跟戒毒似的  小子
You know the Apocalypse is a lot like rehab, kid.
过一天是一天
Just take it one day at a time,
该做什么做什么
and then do the next indicated thing.
眼下  该做的就是找汽油
In this case, that means get more gas.
找完了汽油  谁知道呢
After that, who knows?
我们完蛋了
We're doomed.
不出所料
Well there you have it.
彻底没油了
We're officially on E.
还有多远
How much further?
近在眼前了
Spittin' distance.
泽西恶魔精炼厂
这哪里是精炼厂
That's not a refinery.
简直就是个僵尸工厂
That's a zombie factory.
该死的僵尸
Frackin' zombies.
他们貌似非常迫切地想拿到那边的什么
They seem to want something in there real bad.
是那个声音
It's that sound.
就像蜜蜂闻见花香
Like bees to honey.
或者僵尸闻见尸臭
Or Zs to shit.
你知道是这幅景象吗
Hey, you know about this?
反正你们在别处也找不着汽油了
Hey, all the easy gas is gone.
那你们有什么高见啊
So what's the brilliant plan?
死翘翘  被僵尸啃  早早回老家吗
Die, get eaten, go home early?
这是什么味儿
What's that smell?
僵尸的臭气和汽油味
The undead and gasoline.
都非常易燃
Both highly flammable.
所以绝对不能开火
So no firearms of any kind.
那你打算怎么处理
So how do you want to handle this?
首先我们得想法子让那声音停下来
Well first we got to shut off whatever's making that noise.
可能是油泵之类的
Okay, it's probably some kind of pump.
但是在哪
But where?
跟着僵尸走就是了
Follow the zombies.
他们貌似都朝着油罐架的最上边移动
They all seem to be headed for the top of that catalog.
我们爬上去查查看
We'll get up there and check it out.
我们需要用某种声音把僵尸从气泵那里引开
Then we got to have a sound that draws the Zs away from the pump
这样我们才能取到汽油
so we can get to the gas.
抱歉  我把吉他留在蓝天营了
Sorry, I left my guitar back at Camp Blue Sky.
车喇叭声可以吗
Car horns?
不行  这会把它们都吸引到这个地方来
No, they'll all just head this way.
还有所有能听见这声音的僵尸
And so will every other dead head within earshot.
我有办法
I have something.
僵尸都喜欢高音调的声音
Zs like high-pitched sounds.
越动听的声音它们越喜欢
The more musical the better.
真是每天都能学到新知识
Wow, learn something everyday.
好极了
That's great.
你就是我们的诱饵
You're our decoy.
我跟她一起去
I'll go with her.
我不需要他帮忙
I don't need his help.
不  你需要掩护  跟他一起去
No, you need cover. Take him.
走到架桥的小道上面  再开始放音乐
And start the music when you get to the top of that catwalk.
你们两个  到另外架桥的那一侧
You two, get to the top of the other side
看看能不能关掉那声音  明白了吗
and see if you can kill that noise. Got it.
那孩子去哪了
Where'd that kid go?
一分钟前他还在这里呢
He was here a minute ago.
还有  他的名字是一万
Oh and his name is Ten Thousand.
他最好能在我们动身之前回来
Well he better be back by the time we're ready to go.
如果我们能发动那辆油罐车
Hey, if we get that tanker started
我们就可以从那里加油了
and we could fill it up from the main tank,
这么多油够我们跑到加利福尼亚了
that much gas would get us to California.
我喜欢你这个想法
I like the way you think.
那等下你们都快被烧死的时候
So what should I be doing
我应该做点什么呢
while you all are getting incinerated to death?
好吧  你为何不带卧底先生
All right, why don't you take Mr. Congeniality here
和这辆萨伯曼SUV到安全地带去呢
and the Suburban and get back to a safe distance,
以防万一
just in case.
那如果  你知道的  僵尸回来了怎么办
What if... you know... zombies?
如果我们都不幸出事了
If this all ends in tears,
你一定要带他到加利福尼亚去
you got to get him to California.
我会的
Sure.
没问题
No problem.
稍等一下  朋友  稍等  我会帮你
Wait one second, buddy. Wait one second. I got you.
我们到了
There you go.
很好  让我帮你暖和一下吧
All right, let's warm you up.
外面冷极了  对吧
Oh yeah, it's cold outside, isn't it?
好的  好孩子  好孩子
Yeah. Good boy. Good boy.
你真是疯了
You're crazy.
森夏恩  等等
Sunshine! Hold up!
慢点
Hey! Slow down!
你会把我们俩都害死的
You're gonna get us both killed.
其实只有一个人会死
Actually just one of us.
我知道你想做什么
I know what you're trying to do.
这没用的
It is not gonna work.
你一点也不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
我了解托拜亚斯
I know Tobias
其他家庭成员也不会让你走的  森夏恩
and the rest of the family is never gonna let you leave Sunshine.
我不会再回去了
Well I'm never going back.
还有  我不是森夏恩
And my name isn't Sunshine.
那个女孩早就死了
That girl died a long time ago.
你不明白
You don't understand.
没有你  我不能回去
I can't go back without you.
这可不是对家人该有的态度
That's no way to treat family.
艾迪
Addy.
听着  我就是不相信摩菲
Look, I just don't trust Murphy.
带着那混蛋一起走绝对是个错误
It's all wrong with that dick.
他不只是疯癫而已
He's more than just a little crazy.
这整个任务都疯癫
This whole mission is insane.
沃伦和加内特可不会这么想
Warren and Garnett don't think so.
哈蒙德为了保护他而死
Hammond died trying to protect him,
还有很多人为他而牺牲
and so did a lot of other people.
你也想这样吗
You want to do the same?
不
No.
万一这是真的呢
What if it's true?
万一摩菲真如他们所说的那样
What if Murphy's who they say he is
万一我们真有机会制造出疫苗呢
and there's a chance for a vaccine?
世界已面临末日  没机会补救了  艾迪
You don't get a do-over on the end of the world, Addy.
-已经太晚了  -哪怕只有一丝机会
- It's too late. - If we have the slightest chance
能够唤醒我所熟知的世界
of waking up in the world I remember...
让死者安息
Where dead things stay dead...
我也要抓住这个机会
That's a chance I'm gonna take.
因为那是个希望  麦克
Cuz that's hope, Mack.
你知道我已经有多久没有这样的感觉了吗
You know how long it's been since I've felt something like that?
那不是希望  那是谎话
It's not hope. It's a lie.
这谎话会害死我们的
And it's gonna get us both killed.
那我也情愿因相信这个谎话而死
Well then I'd rather die believing in a lie
总好过没有信仰地苟且活着
than live believing in nothing.
天哪  你说大道理的时候真性感
Damn, you're sexy when you get all philosophical.
继续转啊
Keep cranking.
转出来的能量都能给一座小城市供电了
Cranking enough to light up a small city.
好了
Here.
试试
Try it.
好啦  快点  这车快没油了
Okay, hurry up. It's almost running out of gas.
不用等很久
Not for long.
噪音一停我们就准备走
Get ready to go as soon as they kill that noise.
快点
Come on.
好酷啊
That was cool.
没错  这个坏家伙就是问题所在啊
Yeah. This bad boy's the problem all right.
火跟噪音都是僵尸的最爱
Nothing zombies like more than fire and noise.
是啊  还有人脑
Yeah, except brains.
我们怎么才能关掉这个
How do we turn it off?
制动按钮坏了
Well the stop button doesn't work.
可能是因为压强太大了
Must operate on pressure.
这好像是个减压阀什么的
Like some kind of relief valve or something.
或许我们可以卡住它
Maybe we can jam it up.
那这么高的压强怎么办  从哪儿排出来
Well what about the pressure or whatever it's venting?
我们没工夫四处找原因
Yeah, we don't hang around to find out.
加上油就赶紧跑
Get the gas and get out of dodge.
我们得找根棍子什么的卡住它
We just need something to jam it up with like a pole or something.
不行  这是我的最爱
No! I love this thing.
想别的办法
Figure it out!
喂  那些僵尸
Hey, what happened to all the
爬上来之后发生什么了
zombies that have been coming up here? Huh?
好吧
Okay.
他们成功了
They did it.
行了  准备好
All right. Get ready.
好的
Okay.
我们得走了
We should go.
嗯
Yeah.
小心
Watch out!
太好搞定了
That was handy.
现在总算知道那些僵尸发生什么了
Now we know what happened to the zombies.
好吧  真的该走了
Okay, it's really time to go.
不知道那边怎么样了
Wonder how it's going?
还没听到什么爆响声
Haven't heard anything blow up.
目前为止
Yet.
八
Eights.
抓牌吧
Go fish.
动手
Do it.
好了  行了  现在必须得走了
Okay. Okay. Now it's really time to go.
这儿  宝贝
Here, boy!
你去哪儿了  小家伙
Where did you go, fellow.
嘿  宝贝
Hey, boy.
你在哪儿
Where are you?
过来  狗狗
Come here, doggy.
来吧
Come on.
找到你了
There you are.
你还好吧  宝贝  你想喝点水吗
How are you, boy? Do you want some water?
渴不渴  渴吧
Are you thirsty? Yeah.
来这儿  喝点水
Come here. Let's get some water.
好吧
Yeah.
你渴吗
Are you thirsty?
你是个口渴的小狗狗吧
Are you a thirsty boy?
喝吧
There we go.
这就对了  都喝光  伙计
Yeah, that's right. Drink up, buddy.
喝光光
Drink up.
狗狗
Dog!
狗狗  回来
Dog, come back!
狗狗
Dog!
干得漂亮  上面有什么
Nice job. What was up there?
有个类似于压力控制阀的东西
Some kind of a pressure valve thing.
不过罐里面都是僵尸粘液  都快装满了
But that tank is full of zombie goo, like to the top.
美极了  不过撑不了多久  伙计们
Beautiful. It ain't gonna hold, guys.
放音乐
Start the music!
让我们一齐舞动吧
Let's dance.
我会受到诅咒的
I'll be damned.
我来拿软管
I got the hose.
这儿  给我
Here. Give me that.
准备好了吗
You ready?
启动
Firing up.
我头一回见到有人连打牌都作弊
First time I've ever seen anybody cheat at go fish.
这可是一种天赋
It's a gift.
怎么要搞这么久
What the hell is taking so long?
现在的服务大不如前啊
Full service just ain't what it used to be.
放松点
Relax.
加内特和沃伦心里有数
Garnett and Warren know what they're doing.
这附近僵尸太多了  怪吓人的
Too many Zs around here. It's freaking me out.
我有恐惧症
I got a phobia
你知道的  就是自从我被咬了以后
you know ever since I got bit.
我一直想问你这个  那些咬伤...
I've been meaning to ask you about that. So these bites...
等等  你到底是什么医生
Wait. What kind of doctor are you anyway?
不算是医生  更像个业余药理学家吧
Not really a doctor, more of an amateur pharmacologist.
你呢
What about you?
你怎么会成为人类的救世主的
How'd you get to be the savior of the human race?
你真想知道
You really wanna know?
事实是  对于一个蒙冤的人来说
Truth is for a guy who's been wrongly convicted,
我其实很热心
I'm actually very civic-minded.
我是自愿的
I volunteered.
你们抓错人了  我什么都没干
You got the wrong guy. I didn't do nothin'.
伙计们  正规程序不是这样的
Look, I'm being denied my due process, man!
放我走
Come on. Let me go.
我是无辜的
I'm innocent, man.
放开我
Let me go.
虽然很不好受  但是总有人得挺身而出
It wasn't easy, but somebody had to do it.
天  除非他们把我打个半死
Man, they would have to beat me senseless,
再绑起来  我才会让他们
strap me down, before I'd ever let anybody inject me
把僵尸病毒注射到我身子里
with a live zombie virus.
这不是我个人的问题
Yeah, well it wasn't about me.
你得做你该做的事
You know you do what you got to do.
为了孩子们
For the kids...
所以你注射了疫苗以后
So you... you got the vaccine
再被咬了吗
and then you got bitten?
被咬了八次
Eight times.
天哪
Good God.
非要数的话
If you say so.
肯定很可怕
That must have been horrible.
是啊
Must have been.
幸运的是我晕过去了  什么都记不得了
Luckily I blacked out, so I don't remember any of it.
然后哈蒙德不知怎的就把我救了
Somehow Hammond rescued me.
我想迟来总比不来好
Better late than never, I guess.
后来就一直徒于奔命
And been on the run ever since.
现在哈蒙德也死了
Now Hammond's dead, too.
是啊  死得真是时候
Yep. Good times.
好像来了点鼻子很灵光的伙计
We got some nosey neighbors.
呼叫其他人
Call the others!
你在把它们引过来
You're attracting them!
我们快走
Get us out of here!
闭嘴
Shut up!
好样的
This is great.
你朋友把这灌满
Your friends tank up,
我们再把它拿走
and we take it from them.
没有什么"我们"
There is no we .
我不会回去的
I'm not going back.
只要我还有一口气
Not alive.
你为什么非要作对呢
Why do you keep fighting this?
你知道他不可能让你走的
You know he's never gonna let you go.
我什么都做得出来
I will do whatever I have to do.
你要做什么
You'll do what?!
告诉你的新朋友我的身份吗
Tell your new friends who I am?
要是我告诉他们你是谁的话会怎么样
What happens when I tell them what you are?!
不  天哪
No! God!
天哪  兄弟
Good grief, dude.
摩菲  好吧
Murphy, all right.
摩菲  摩菲
Murphy. Murphy.
看着我
Look at me.
看着我的眼睛
In my eyes.
你在这里很安全
You're safe in here man.
他们抓不到你
They can't get you.
做几个深呼吸  伙计
Now just try to breathe through it, man.
深呼吸
Breathe.
就在那里  就在那里
Right there. Right there.
够了  这只有两个僵尸而已
All right, that's enough. Look, there's only two of them.
伙计  我现在就出去
Look man, I'm gonna go out there.
我会把它们赶走
I'm gonna draw them away
一个个都干掉
and I'm gonna mercy them.
现在你给我冷静下来
Now you just... just chill out.
为什么事事都要大费周章
Why is nothing ever easy?
行了  跟我来孩子们
Okay, follow me boys!
快来
Come on!
鲜肉哦
Fresh meat.
真厚道啊
Oh, nice guy.
你感觉到了吗
Did you feel that?
你听
Listen.
回卡车里去
Get in the truck!
动作快
Come on!
小狗
Hey, boy!
妈的
Damn it.
蠢货
Hey, stupid!
你不会想要他的
You don't want him.
他已经快被咬烂了
He's all chewed up already.
来吧  伙计  来吧
Come on, friend. Come on.
快张嘴来吃你的老朋友多克
Raise your chin for your ol' pal Doc.
撑住  摩菲  它们够不着你的
Hang in there, Murphy! They can't get you!
一千零五十八
One thousand fifty eight.
让它们走开
Get them off!
一千零五十九
One thousand fifty nine.
一千零六十  射得好  小哥
One thousand sixty! Nice shot, kid!
摩菲
Murphy!
罗伯塔
Hey, Roberta.
我没法把这个该死的油管弄下来
I can't get this damn hose off.
我们得快点撤
We got to get going.
快下去  快下去
Get off! Get off!
快下去
Get off!
那是摩菲吗
Is that Murphy?
很不幸  是他
Unfortunately, yes.
快从这里撤退  撤退  快走
Get out of here. Get out of here! Go!
快
Come on!
等一下  你准备做什么
Wait a minute. What are you gonna do?
我要救摩菲  快走  你快撤
I got to save Murphy. Come on. Get out of here.
滚开  特拉维斯
Get out of my way, Travis.
不要逼我杀你
I don't want to have to kill you.
这当然没问题
That's not gonna be a problem.
是时候回老家了  森夏恩
It's time to go home, Sunshine.
你忘了
You forget.
我早就习惯了
I'm used to it.
懦夫
Coward!
妈的
Shit!
不要
No!
放开它你这只死狗
Get off of him you bastard!
停下
Stop!
你不能杀了我这一年来
You're not gonna kill the only living thing
唯一见过的一个活物
I've seen in a year!
快下车
Got to get out of here.
不行  僵尸太多了  我不能下车
No! There's too many! I can't!
-快点  -你不懂
- Come on! - You don't understand!
我不下车  我不行
I can't. I can't.
不行
I can't.
你行的  没时间了
Yes! It is not the time!
不  不要  我不行
No! No! I can't!
这里要爆炸了
This is gonna explode!
你不明白  我不行
You don't understand! I can't!
电影里要来的轻松得多
This works easier in the movies.
一千零六十二
One thousand sixty two.
快走
Come on.
我还活着
I'm alive?
你  你竟然还活着  难以置信
You're... you're still alive. No way.
你还活着
You're still alive.
我还活着
I'm still alive.
吃我一木条  疯狗
Yeah! Yeah, take that Cujo!
我说到做到
That's what I'm talkin' about!
我们成功了小狗  我跟你  我们办到了
We did it, pup. Me and you, we did it.
我们还活着
We're alive.
只剩下你和我了  小狗  只有你和我
It's just you and me, pup. Just you and me.
好  我有汉堡排和牛肉三明治
Okay. I've got beef patty and sloppy joe.
我觉得你更喜欢牛肉
You look like a beef eater to me.
好  给你
Okay. Here we go.
这绝对是我最棒的首次约会之一
This is actually one of the best first dates I've ever had.
给  很好  看起来很好吃是吧
Here we go. Oh yeah, doesn't that look good?
慢点吃  伙计
Whoa. Slow down, dude.
我只有十年的储备食物
I only have ten year supply.
伙计
Dude?
这不算什么好名字  对吧
That's not a very good name, is it?
我们来起个更好  行吗  叫"花花公子"怎么样
Nah, we can do better than that, can't we? What about "the dude"?
我很喜欢那部电影
I really like that movie.
不要吗  我们可以想出更好的
No? Yeah, we can come up with something better than that.
好  乖孩子
Yes. Good boy.
那是什么
What is that?
看起来好像有人在玩火柴
Looks like somebody's been playing with matches.
那是哪  是炼油厂吗
What is that? Is that a refinery?
我们拿到汽油了吗
So did we get the gas?
太好了  刚才谁引起的爆炸
Great. Who screwed that up?
抱歉
Sorry.
你的朋友哪去了
So where's your friend?
他没能生还  而且他也不是我的朋友
He didn't make it. And he wasn't my friend.
喂
Hello?
喂  是我  来自北极光的市民Z广播
Hello. It's me, Citizen Z from Northern Light.
你是哪位
To whom am I speaking?
查理·加内特中士
Sergeant Charlie Garnett.
太好了
Excellent.
很高兴又和你讲话  长官
Good talking to you again sir.
你们怎么样了
How's it going?
还可以
It's going.
很好  包裹怎么样
Excellent. And the package?
还活着
Still alive.
请告诉我们  要把他送到哪去
Please tell us where to drop him off.
加利福尼亚
California.
加利福尼亚  等等  不
California? Wait. No.
等等  那不可能
Hold on. That's not gonna happen.
我们需要个近一点的地方
We need to go some place closer.
近一点
Closer?
抱歉中士  没有近一点的地方
Sorry Sergeant, but there is no... closer.
我能跟你的上司说话吗
Can I speak to someone in charge?
是的我懂  我相信他们也很想跟你讲话
Yeah, copy that. I'm sure they'd like to talk to you too.
可是也许有困难
But that may be a little problematic.
有困难是什么意思
What do you mean problematic?
又有小伙伴儿过来了
More puppies and kittens.
我为什么不能跟实验室的人说话
Why can't I speak to somebody at the lab?
长官
Well, sir.
到底怎么了
What's going on?!
我们失去联系了
We've lost contact.
他们还活着吗
Are they even still alive?
我正在努力确认  长官
I'm working on confirming that, sir.
我看到屏幕上全是僵尸  朝你们来了
I've got a screen full of incoming Zs headed your way.
你最好快走  中士
You'd better get moving, Sergeant.
我会找到你们  目前就一直西进至大海吧
I'll find you. But for now, go west till you hit the ocean.
喂
Hello?
加内特中士
Sergeant Garnett?
中士
Sergeant?
我知道
I know.
我知道  可我们只能指望他们了
I know. But they're the only chance we got.
我需要来点音乐
I need some music.
真是好孩子
That's a good boy.
看
Look.
太棒了
Awesome.
我以为再也见不到它了呢
Never thought I would see this thing again.
等等  那孩子来了
Wait! Here comes the kid!
我找到了这个
Found these.
宝贝
Kid.
你简直是救世主
You're a god.
是啊  快点了
Yeah well hurry up.
不好意思  女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
你头发里插了根手指
You have a finger in your hair.